twibble.io 2019-01-25

# Twibble - Privacy Policy — Twibble

## EFFECTIVE May 25, 2018

This Privacy Policy describes the "Personal Information" about you that Twibble, Inc. (“Twibble” or “we” or "the Service") collects through this website (the “Site”), as well as how that information is used, maintained, and, in some cases, shared. This Personal Information means any information relating to an identified or identifiable individual, and we obtain such Personal Information relating to you from various sources as described below.

At Twibble, we respect your data security and privacy and are committed to protecting you through compliance with this policy. This policy describes the type of information that we may collect from you, or that you may provide to us, when you use or visit the Twibble website at https://twibble.io or https://home.twibble.io including all related webpages, subdomains, or otherwise use the Twibble service. This policy also describes our practices, meaning how we collect, use, maintain, protect, and disclose this Personal Information.

If you do not provide Personal Information when Twibble asks you for such information, you may be unable to use the Service if that requested information is necessary in order for us to provide the service to you, or if we are legally required to collect it in order to provide the service to you.

Please note that by using this Site, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Site.

Personal Information is collected from you when you register with the Service, connect your social media accounts to Twibble, communicate with Twibble customer support, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, fill out a form, survey, or other such online marketing or informational or questionnaire, or similar such material, connect your website or blog to the Service, or when you otherwise provide such Personal Information to us. We also may collect information automatically as you navigate through, and use, the Service. Such automatically collected information may include usage details, IP addresses, and information collected through cookies and other tracking technologies.

We may use the Personal Information we obtain about you to:

  * create and manage your account, provide our Service and respond to your communications;
  * manage account authentication;
  * communicate with you to verify your account and for informational and operational purposes, such as account management, customer service, or system maintenance, including by periodically emailing you service-related announcements;
  * tailor our Service (e.g., we may use cookies and similar technologies to remember your preferences);
  * post your content and messages on social media platforms;
  * aggregate your Personal Information for analytical purposes;
  * provide customer support;
  * operate, analyze and improve our business;
  * send you marketing communications about Twibble products, services, offers, programs and promotions;
  * keep the Service safe and secure;
  * manage our customer, service provider and partner relationships;
  * enforce our agreements related to our Service and our other legal rights;
  * comply with applicable legal requirements, industry standards and our policies;
  * process transactions;
  * administer contests, promotions, surveys or other site features; and
  * provide you with notices about your account and subscription, including expiration and renewal notices.

It's also possible that we may use the Personal Information that we obtain from you in some other ways that we would describe to you when you provide the Personal Information, and for any other purpose, but always only with your consent.

If you are located in the European Economic Area, we may process your Personal Information for the above purposes when:

  * you have consented to the use of your Personal Information, For example, we may seek to obtain your consent for our uses of cookies or similar technologies, or to send you marketing communications.
  * we need your Personal Information to provide you with services and products requested by you, or to respond to your inquiries,
  * we have a legal obligation to use your Personal Information, or
  * we have a legitimate interest in using your Personal Information. In particular, we have a legitimate interest in using your Personal Information to ensure and improve the safety, security, and performance of our Service, to anonymize Personal Information and carry out data analyses.

The following describes the types of personal and other information we may collect about you, and how we use and maintain that information:

 _Registration._   Before you can fully utilize the Service, you must register with Twibble by logging in with your Twitter, Inc. ("Twitter") credentials, and by providing us with your email address. ** ** For more information, please see below. We request all of the foregoing information for identification purposes, to communicate with you regarding your account, to collect payment for the Service, and to facilitate the Service. We may keep this information indefinitely. You may optionally choose to grant Twibble access to post on behalf of your various Facebook Page(s) by authenticating your Facebook account with your Facebook credentials ("Facebook").

 _Correspondence._ ** ** If you correspond with us through the Site (or via email), we may gather the communications that you submit in a file specific to you. We may keep this information indefinitely.

 _URL and IP addresses._ ** ** Like many other websites, Twibble collects information about users’ utilization and navigation of the Site. This information helps us to design the Site to better suit our users’ needs. For example, the Site will track the URL that you visited before you came to the Site, the URL to which you next go and your Internet Protocol (IP) address. We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer the Site. Your IP address also is used to help identify you and to gather broad demographic information.

 _Information Collected With Cookies._ **  **Like many websites, Twibble also uses cookies on certain pages of the Site. Cookies make using the Internet easier by, among other things, saving your preferences for you. For example, a cookie lets the Site remember that you have registered, which allows us to speed up your future activities at the Site, and which allows you to enter your registration information less frequently while visiting the Site. We may also use cookies to deliver content tailored to your interests. Our cookies may enable us to relate your use of the Site to personally identifying information that you previously submitted, such as calling you by name when you return to the Site. If your browser is set to reject cookies, or if your browser notifies you that you are about to receive a cookie and you reject it, then your use of the Site may not be as efficient or as enjoyable as it would be if the cookie were enabled. The information that we collect with cookies allows us to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to statistically analyze the Site usage, to improve our content and product offerings and to customize the Site’s content and layout.

Twibble will not share, rent, sell or otherwise disclose any of the personally identifiable information that we collect about you, except when we have your permission or in any of the following situations:

  * We may disclose to other users of the Service the personally identifiable information about you that we collect and your Profile information, as needed for the proper facilitation of the Service, such as your Twitter account name(s) or Facebook account or Facebook Page name(s), but _not_  your email address(es).

  * We may disclose information that we collect about you to unaffiliated third-party contractors, to enable such third parties to perform functions on our behalf in making available the Site and/or the Service or to complete or confirm a transaction that you conduct with us.   

  * We may disclose the results of aggregated data about you for marketing or promotional purposes (for instance, that a certain percentage of out Site’s users are living in the United States). In these situations, we do not disclose to these entities any information that could be used to personally identify you.

  * Information about you in Twibble’s possession may also be disclosed as part of any merger, acquisition, sale of company assets, or transition of service to another provider, as well as in the unlikely event of insolvency, bankruptcy, or receivership in which your personal information would be transferred as one of the business assets of the company. We do not guarantee that any entity receiving such information in connection with one of these transactions will comply with all the terms of this Privacy Policy.

  * Twibble will comply with any subpoena, court order or other legal process requesting any of the information about you in our possession, and Twibble may use such information to establish or exercise our legal rights, or to defend against legal claims.

More specifically, we may share the Personal Information we collect about you as described below or otherwise disclosed to you at the time the information is collected, including with:

 **Social Media Platforms**

Our main purpose for collecting Personal Information is to allow you to post content on social platforms and enable you to track metrics for analytical purposes. We may allow you to link your Twibble account with an account on a third party social network platform, such as Facebook or Twitter, and to transfer your information to and from the applicable third party platform. Once you share your content to a social media platform, its use will be governed by that platform’s privacy policy.

 **Service Providers**

We engage certain trusted third parties to perform functions and provide services to us, including hosting and maintenance, error monitoring, debugging, performance monitoring, billing, customer relationship, database storage and management, and direct marketing campaigns. We may share your Personal Information with these third parties, but only to the extent necessary to perform these functions and provide such services. We also require these third parties to maintain the privacy and security of the Personal Information they process on our behalf.

 **Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement**

Twibble cooperates with government and law enforcement officials or private parties to enforce and comply with the law. To the extent permitted under applicable law, we may disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we believe is necessary or appropriate to investigate, respond to, and defend against claims, for legal process (including subpoenas), to protect the property and rights of Twibble or a third party, to protect Twibble against liability, for the safety of the public or any person, to prevent or stop any illegal, unethical, fraudulent, abusive, or legally actionable activity, to protect the security or integrity of the Service and any equipment used to make the Service available, or to comply with the law.

 **Business Transfers**

We may sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of our assets, including Personal Information, in connection with a merger, acquisition, reorganization, sale of assets, or similar transaction, or in the event of insolvency or bankruptcy. You will have the opportunity to opt out of any such transfer if the new entity’s planned processing of your information differs materially from that set forth in this Privacy Policy.

 **Other Third Parties**

We may share Personal Information with affiliates and business partners to whom it is reasonably necessary or desirable for us to disclose your data for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy. We may also make certain non-Personal Information available to third parties for various purposes, including for business or marketing purposes or to assist third parties in understanding our users’ interest, habits, and usage patterns for certain programs, content, services, advertisements, promotions, and functionality available through the Service.

Twibble is based in the United States of America. If you use the Site outside of the United States, information that we collect about you will be transferred to servers inside the United States and maintained indefinitely, which may involve the transfer of information out of countries located in the European Economic Area. By allowing Twibble to collect information about you, you consent to such transfer and processing of your data.

To help protect the privacy of data you transmit through the Site, where personally identifiable information is requested, Twibble uses technology designed to encrypt the information that you input before it is sent to us. In addition, Twibble takes steps intended to protect the user data we collect against unauthorized access. However, you should keep in mind that the Site is run on software, hardware and networks, any component of which may, from time to time, require maintenance or experience problems or breaches of security beyond our control. 

Please also be aware that despite our best intentions and the guidelines outlined in this Privacy Policy, no data transmission over the Internet or encryption method can be guaranteed to be 100% secure.

You may correct or update information collected about you through the Site by managing your account profile or by contacting Twibble at the email or mailing address noted below. We will update our records as promptly as possible. For our records, we may retain original and updated information for reasons such as technical constraints, dispute resolution, troubleshooting and agreement enforcement.

This Privacy Policy only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you through the Site. You should be aware that when you are on the Site, you may be directed to other websites that are beyond our control, and Twibble is not responsible for the privacy practices of third parties or the content of linked websites. We encourage you to read the privacy policy posted on any third-party website that you visit. 

If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive such marketing communications from us, please follow the unsubscribe instructions provided in any of the communications. Please be aware that, even after you opt out from receiving marketing messages from us, you will continue to receive administrative messages from Twibble regarding the Service.

In certain jurisdictions you have the right to request access and receive information about the Personal Information we maintain about you, to update and correct inaccuracies in your Personal Information, to restrict or object to the processing of your Personal Information, to have the information blocked, anonymized or deleted, as appropriate, or to exercise your right to data portability to transfer your Personal Information to another company. Those rights may be limited in some circumstances by local law requirements. In addition to the above-mentioned rights, you also have the right to lodge a complaint with a competent supervisory authority subject to applicable law.

Where required by law, we obtain your consent for the processing of certain Personal Information collected by cookies or similar technologies, or used to send you direct marketing communications, or when we carry out other processing activities for which consent may be required. If we rely on consent for the processing of your Personal Information, you have the right to withdraw it at any time and free of charge. When you do so, this will not affect the lawfulness of the processing before your consent withdrawal.

To update your preferences, ask us to remove your information from our mailing lists, delete your account or submit a request to exercise your rights under applicable law, please contact us as specified in the “Contact Us” section below.

Residents of California have the right to request a disclosure describing what types of personal information we have shared with third parties for their direct marketing purposes, and with whom we have shared it, during the preceding year. You may request a copy of that disclosure by contacting us as indicated below.

The Service is intended for visitors located within the United States. We make no representation that the Service is appropriate or available for use outside of the United States. Access to the Service from countries or territories or by individuals where such access is illegal is prohibited

We do not knowingly collect or maintain personally identifiable information from persons under 18 years old, and no part of the Site is directed to persons under 18. IF YOU ARE UNDER 18 YEARS OF AGE, PLEASE DO NOT USE OR ACCESS THE SITE AT ANY TIME OR IN ANY MANNER. If Twibble learns that personally identifiable information of any person under 18 years old has been collected without verifiable parental consent, then Twibble will take the appropriate steps to delete this information. If you are a parent or guardian and discover that your child under the age of 18 has obtained a Twibble account, then you may alert Twibble at the address below and request that we delete that child’s personal information from our systems.

If you access the Site as a representative of a third party, such as your employer, that party may review and modify your personal information, ask us to delete your personal information, or request that we cease collecting your personal information. If such a third party asks us to delete your personal information or cease collecting your personal information, we may terminate your right to access the Site.

By choosing to visit the Site or otherwise provide information to Twibble, you agree that any dispute over privacy or the terms contained in this Privacy Policy will be governed by the laws of the State of California. You also agree to abide by any limitation on damages contained in our Terms of Use (available here) or other agreement that we may have with you.

Twibble reserves the right to update this Privacy Policy from time to time. Please visit this page periodically so that you will be apprised of any changes. 

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, or need to reach us for any other reason, you may contact us by e-mail at [contact@twibble.io](mailto:contact@twibble.io), or by postal mail at: 

Twibble, Inc.  
PO Box 1351  
Tiburon, CA 94920-2366  
USA

 _Last Updated:  May 25, 2018_
